# Cornelius Venti

corneliusventi@gmail.com

+6289688130986

linkedin.com/in/corneliusventi

https://corneliusventi.dev

## Summary

I'm a Javascript Engineer with four years of Full Stack Development. I worked in industries such as Software House (2 years), E-commerce (1 year) and Insurance (2 years).

Skills that I learned during four years of Full Stack Development such as Typescript (2 years), Next.js (1 year), React.js (1 year), Nuxt.js (3 years), Vue.js (3 years), Nest.js (2 years), Node.js (1 year), HTML (4 years), CSS (4 years) and Javascript (4 years).

I already work on projects such as a regional financial management site, an online tax reporting site, a letter approval & electronic signature site, an e-commerce site, a lead generation form & microservice, a logging module, a partnership API, an email & report microservice and a promotion's back-office site.

## **Experience**



### Full Stack Developer

**FWD** Insurance

Oct 2020 - Present (1 year 10 months +)

I am responsible for building projects that use by customers and partners. These were projects that I built:

- Lead Generation Form (Vue.js as Web Component and Nestjs as Backend/Microservice),
- Logger Modules For Microservice (Wiston as Logger Modules and AWS CloudWatch as Logger Service),
- Ryde App Partnership API (Mulesoft),
- Email/Report Microservice (Nestjs as Backend, Html-pdf as Report Generator and SendGrid as Email Provider)
- Back Office Promotion Management (Nestjs as Backend, Nextjs as Frontend and Material UI for UI)

### Staff Development

Satumarket

Feb 2020 - Sep 2020 (8 months)

Built Local E-commerce at Pontianak from scratch using Nuxtis, Laravel, and Flutter within three months

#### Web Developer

Orange Multimedia CV.

Feb 2018 - Feb 2020 (2 years 1 month)

Built three Web Application Systems using Laravel for the local government department in Pontianak.

- These were projects that I created:
- SETIL (Letter System Based on Electronic Signatures)
- SIPKD (Regional Financial Management Information System)

- OTR (Online Tax Reporting System)

#### **Education**



# **Walter** Universitas Tanjungpura

Bachelor of Computer Science, Informatics

Jun 2015 - Aug 2019

I graduated from Tanjungpura University with a Bachelor of Computer Science with a graduation date of October 2019. I graduated with an undergraduate thesis about "On-Street and Off-Street Car Parking Management System Based on Location-Based Service (LBS) and Google Maps API".

### **Skills**

TypeScript • Next.js • React.js • Nuxt.js • Vue.js • NestJS • Node.js • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript